Our Hearts as One:
Our World to Create, Together!
Morning!
Good morning.
Gelu-lu!
Gelu-lu.
You're a vision today like usual, DD.
A Star Rookie in the Drag Queen World:
DD
Aw, c'mon.
Millio-chan, you're such a flirt.
Huh? OD-san's not on.
So, today, let's start by talking
about the prohibition of CROWDS.
DD's nice.
It's just a sign of the times.
CROWDS Prohibition Confirmed!
Gel-chan might say, "CROWDS, no way."
CROWDS use has now become illegal.
What do you think, DD?
Isn't the Gatchaman's
popularity in jeopardy?
I think that's a good thing.
I mean, CROWDS is way too dangerous!
Well, popularity has nothing
to do with what we do...
Oh, DD! That pose!
It's been popular lately.
CROWDS Prohibition Confirmed!
Everyone knows this, right?
Yeah! Gelu-lu!
Gel-chan started this Gel-sign.
Gelu-lu: The Gel-Sign Super Fad
Prime Minister Sadra Unstoppable
It's how we signal each other
when strangers help each other
and their hearts become one.
Can you make this sign, Pai-Pai?
Maybe that's why,
Quit it.
but everyone making the Gel-sign
gives off a really happy vibe!
Gelu-lu!
Forget the V sign!
This sign's the way to go!
Hasn't it been all about Gel lately?
Is this how we use it?
But viewers!
Do we know any other prime minister
who's enjoyed as much support as him?
He's right! Gel's pretty impressive.
Not to mention,
thanks to Gel-chan's influence,
Kids, your future is looking bright!
people are helping each other,
regardless of gender or age.
Gelu-lu!
Simply put, what was previously
occurring on GALAX
is now occurring in actual society.
This is a huge development!
Plus, the smart phone votes are making
the people's lives easier by the day.
GALAX's obsolete now
Shouldn't it just be used for voting?
I feel the Sadra leadership will remain
stable for the foreseeable future.
GALAX's obsolete now
Shouldn't it just be used for voting?
I get nostalgic
thinking about the times
we used CROWDS to help people..
GALAX's obsolete now
Shouldn't it just be used for voting?
I get nostalgic
thinking about the times
we used CROWDS to help people.
Just Gel it in the city. lol
GALAX's obsolete now
Shouldn't it just be used for voting?
I get nostalgic
thinking about the times
we used CROWDS to help people.
Just Gel it in the city. lol
Nah, I'm still a little embarrassed to do it.
I'm rather afraid.
Afraid? Of what?
Of what people are doing right now—
I'd like to think it's because
everyone is personally driven,
but I wonder if it's just a passing fad.
I wonder if we're pushing change too fast.
I remember how you used to be
so keen on "updating" the world.
It's strange to hear you say that.
I've learned a lot.
It's a necessary evil. It's just backlash.
Backlash?
Yeah, backlash against
what we've been doing.
It was too soon for CROWDS.
It resulted in conflict,
and that, in turn, created a
reactionary drive for peace.
We're the ones who acted too soon.
So you're saying that it wasn't
VAPE who threatened peace, but me?
Are you referring to Suzuki Rizumu?
Yes.
But I haven't given up yet.
It's true that anyone can use CROWDS.
In a way, that may have
been irresponsible of me.
But the easy access is what
broadens participation
and increases the odds of it being
sustainable over the long run.
Some day, people will rise to the challenge
and CROWDS will be needed again—
Rui!
Forget about CROWDS for now.
Backlash always dies down quickly.
Gelsadra isn't the one
who'll protect world peace.
It's us.
Hey, you're getting way too close!
Maybe I should sue him.
OD, you look serious...
Okay, breathe in deeper!
Okay.
Gelu-lu....
Gelu-lu...
Gel-chan, are you okay?
You okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Well, people do tell me
I look pale these days.
Our Hearts as One!
Create Our World, Together!
That's no big surprise there.
Gel-chan's working so hard
that he doesn't sleep or eat.
I'll work as long as I must
if I can unite everyone's heart.
Fortunately, my home planet
doesn't have the custom of sleep,
natto, or melon bread.
You're lucky that your
prime minister's an alien.
Huh? Utsutsu-chan, is something wrong?
I'm gloomy.
Wings of Eight, gather at
the Spiritual Precipice.
The scarlet angel
will, in time, transform,
and gentle beasts will appear.
Their names are many.
Gentle beasts?
Lord JJ!
Can you be a little less vague?
Wow! They're beautiful, Senpai!
Right...
Hmm... "Scarlet" again.
Jou-san, what do you think?
He said "scarlet" again.
That bothers me, too.
But it can't be VAPE this time.
Suzuki Rizumu's NOTE has been...
I have put it away in a place
no one knows for safekeeping!
Cough, cough.
The only other thing that's red is...
Huh?
But I'm blue.
Tsubasa-chan, how's Gel-chan doing?
He's doing great!
I guess he's being told
he looks a little pale lately,
but, uh, that's just him joking like usual.
Oh, red...
Has anything changed about Gel-chan?
No. Nothing in particular.
Really?
Really!
Gel-chan's doing fine today, too!
You all must be feeling
his awesome influence every day!
Yeah, it is powerful right now.
Some people say
his popularity is just a fad,
but I don't think so.
I think everyone's tired.
Tired?
Tired of what?
Tired of a world with never-ending conflict.
They've witnessed such a world
since the day they were born,
so everyone's come to realize
that we should really unite our hearts
and create a peaceful world.
Yes, that's wonderful!
It's so wonderful that
it makes me a bit anxious.
If they're so fixated on maintaining peace
that they stop saying what they want to say,
that's not good.
I'm gloomy...
It'll be fine!
Look how well it's going right now!
Don't you agree, Sugane-senpai?
Huh?
Well, sure.
My friends all seem happier than before.
It does seem like we're
moving in a good direction.
Thank you!
But, Tsubasa-chan.
I'd like you to tell Sadra-kun
to not rush change too much.
Okay...
Oh, I have to prep for
a smart phone vote with Gel-chan,
so I should get going!
What, Senpai?
Tsubasa-chan, is Gel-chan really okay?
Of course he is.
I said he is!
Miss, don't forget that while
Gelsadra has become the prime minister,
he remains under our observation.
Right.
I'm with him, so it's fine.
I'm a Gatchaman, too.
Tsubasa-chan, we're part of the same team.
If anything happens,
please tell us right away!
Roger!
Hey, guys!
Why do you all look worried?
The newbie's working hard
with Gelsadra every day!
Thanks to them,
this planet may finally emerge
from protective observation status!
Pai-Pai, are you sure it's not
just you wanting to get credit?
Of course not!
I wonder what "their names
are many" is supposed to mean.
Katze-san.
You seem sleepy lately.
Sorry, sorry.
I got sleepy all of a sudden.
Katze-san, what's your opinion of Gel-chan?
Let me see... I'll be seriously honest.
He's a piece of shit.
I think he can go die in a fire.
So you don't like him?
When I told him that,
he got all teary-eyed. lol.
Huh?
You've met Gel-chan before?
Sure.
He's super famous.
Really?
So did you guys fight?
Of course not! It'd never get to that!
What do you mean?
Oh, c'mon, Hajime-tan.
Don't play dumb.
Hey, are you stupid?
Are you stupid, Hajime-tan?
Or are you just being a bitch?
Which is it?
Hey, hey, hey.
Are you just being a bitch?
What is it, huh?
Hmm...
What is it?
Hmm!
Hey, hey, hey.
Gel-lu...
Why won't the colors
and shapes become one yet?
Are you okay?
Is something worrying you?
Is there anything I can do?
Being lonely is so lame!
They're so creepy!
Why?
I'm trying so hard.
Gelu-lu...
Gel-chan, why don't you get some rest?
I'm fine.
See? I'm fine.
Well, you do look healthier than yesterday.
Right?
But if you're worried about anything,
you can talk to me about anything!
Gel-chan?
Tsubasa-chan, I'm sad.
What's wrong?
Look.
Right!
No way!
Everyone as one... lol
That's just impossible
I'm trying so hard every day, but...
It'll be okay!
Everyone will come around eventually.
I'll always be on your side, no matter what!
Thanks...
What's wrong with you?
Huh?
What's wrong with what, Jou-san?
Well, his body.
Huh?
Everyone's way too worried.
He's the same Gel-chan
we all know and love, right?
A single tear just slid
down Gel-chan's cheek.
"Why aren't everyone's hearts united?"
Falling silent after asking us that question,
his eyes brimmed
with tears mourning the world.
Don't cry, Gel-chan!
Don't let this get to you!
It'll only take a little longer.
We'll try hard, too!
Gel-chan, do you see that?
Do you hear that?
Gelu-lu...
I see.
I get it now, everyone.
Gel-chan?
Tsubasa-chan, I'll be fine now.
Thank you!
Studio 3: Broadcast Schedule      July
Limit?
What's that?
Everyone!
Just now, Gel-chan proposed a new idea!
From this day forward, there will be
a third option during smart phone votes.
In addition to "Right!" and "No Way!",
there will be "Let Sadra Handle It"!
Right!     No Way!     Let Sadra Handle It.
This is Gel-chan's decision
after he thought long and hard
about how to make everyone's hearts into one.
Right, Gel-chan!
Right!
Right, right!
Millio-chan, you're way too hyper!
I see.
I can see letting Gelsadra
handle things now. Yep!
Wow! He's grown a lot!
The Millione Show: New Option in  Smart Phone Voting
The "Let Sadra Handle It" Button
It's just like Jou-chan said.
You wouldn't understand.
When you become a leader, you develop poise.
Cough, cough.
Pai-Pai, you're way too dense!
I'm gloomy...
The angel's changed.
This is bad news.
Is More Child Assistance Necessary?
Let Sadra Handle It
This works.
I mean, it's Gel-chan.
I feel like a weight's been
lifted off our shoulders.
Regarding the newly introduced
"let Sadra handle it" button,
Is More Child Assistance Necessary?
Let Sadra Handle It
Yup, let our hero, Sadra, handle it!
it's already received positive
reviews for being very convenient.
Let Sadra handle it!
Handle it!
What do you think about this reception,
Prime Minister Sadra?
Yuru-jii, I'll click for you—
"Handle it."
Don't.
Yes, I hope this will relieve
people of their burden
I can think for myself.
Oh, you're so stubborn.
and help more people smile in this nation.
Yuru-jii, you should talk to
Tsubasa on the phone sometimes.
"Our hearts as one, create our world, together" remains my slogan.
She's working really hard.
Let Sadra Handle It (94%)
Right! (4%)
No way! (2%)
So this is what everyone really wanted.
Why didn't I realize this sooner?
Are you okay, Gel-chan?
Yep. I'm fine.
We're almost there, Tsubasa-chan.
Yeah.
Sadra-kun, please cancel
the change you made today.
But I did it because everyone wanted it—
If you do this,
everyone will stop thinking,
and the world will rapidly devolve!
Are you talking about
something difficult again?
No, Tsubasa-chan.
I don't really understand difficult stuff,
but I think the world right now
is a much better world than
when CROWDS were in it!
Look how peaceful the world
has become, even without CROWDS.
Gel-chan's working hard,
and everyone believes in him.
Tsubasa-chan, you don't understand—
If I may,
I think I understand the
world and the people in it
a lot better than you, Rui-senpai!
Gel-chan...
Gel-chan also realized how everyone feels.
Everyone's been worried for a long time
because their hearts wouldn't become one.
You can't rush this.
I told you this.
Tsubasa-chan, even if it's
the right thing to do,
if you rush it too much,
you'll trip and fall!
But it's what we decided as a nation!
But that'd mean individual
motivation will never develop,
and the world will never be updated.
Please stop, please.
Gel-chan.
This may be conflict,
but it's nothing to be sad about.
Everyone's just searching
for their own answer.
You shouldn't be afraid.
But I am.
I'm afraid that someone
will shatter everyone's hearts
now that they're finally one.
Please stop, Senpai.
Look what you're doing to Gel-chan.
I don't think I can become one with you guys.
Tsubasa-chan, what becoming one means is—
Like you said, I'm just me.
Even if I won't be accepted as a Gatchaman,
I'll believe in everyone with Gel-chan.
If that's what you think...
Yes?
Resign from the Gatchaman right now.
Okay.
Tsubasa-chan.
No matter what people say to me,
I'll protect the peace in Japan
in a way different than yours.
Tsubasa-chan.
Tsubasa-chan, no.
The Gatchaman need you, Tsubasa-chan.
That's what I'll always believe!
Senpai...
Thank you for having me!
Well, we don't have a choice.
Newbie!
Gelsadra!
Take good care of this planet.
I'm gloomy...
"The Gatchaman need you, Tsubasa-chan!"
Shut up, Katze-san!
Hey, you stupid ass, naive Gatcha guys!
Katze-san's saying something.
You think you can win against that red pig?
Keep on dreaming!
Even I ran away, shitting my pants!
Gatchaman's finished,
I'm gloomy.
really finished,
Berg-Katze...
lololololololol.
You ran?
Gatchaman's finished,
real finished.
All together now, everyone!
I see.
That's a dangerous turn of events.
Still, you're coming to me for help?
Is the world ending?
Well, I can see why.
Having a power no one else has can be lonely.
I just want you to think about it with me.
Think about what?
About this country's future.
Yeah, right.
My role in this is finished.
There's nothing left for me to think about.
I'm an ape just like everyone else.
You're not an ape.
Both you and I
are human beings,
concerned for this nation's future.
I know that's what you
also believe, deep down.
You don't give up, do you?
Well, a word of advice, then.
Everyone will become real apes now.
What do you mean?
Think.
You said you're not an ape, didn't you?
It'll all happen in a flash.
Be ready. Prepare yourself.
It hurts...
I can't swallow or inhale any more.
What was that just now?
Gelu-lu...