А?
Эм...
Цубаса.
Цубаса-тян, посмотри сюда!
А?
Как ощущения?
Можешь показать нам какие-нибудь приёмы?
Расскажи нам побольше!
Я же сказала!
Пока вы говорите все сразу,
я не смогу ни на что ответить!
Цубаса!
Круто выглядишь!
Врёшь!
Эй, новенькая!
Новенькая?!
Т-то есть, я?
Теперь ты стала одной из нас.
Приложи усилия!
Ладно!
Хорошо!
Твоим ментором выберем...
тебя, Хаджиме!
О, меня?
Понятно!
Цубаса-тян, рада сотрудничеству с тобой!
Я тоже рада сотрудничеству с Вами, семпай!
Наконец-то, завтра начинаются
выборы мэра Тачикавы!
проникновение
Голосуйте своим большим пальцем
Первые выборы посредством смартфонов в истории!
Выборы мэра города Тачикава
Мы можем предложить вам помощь,
если у вас возникли затруднения при голосовании.
Если у вас нет планшета,
мы можем предоставить его вам бесплатно,
Держите.
если вы покажете соответствующее удостоверение!
Тоскливо.
Джо-сан,
вы можете помедленее?
Извините.
Эй, научите нас тоже!
Есть приложение для голосования,
так что сначала скачайте его.
Эй, Сугане-кун.
А у тебя правда есть девушка?
Мы слышали, что она учится с тобой
в одной группе в колледже
Нет, это неправда.
Кто распустил этот слух?
Не отвлекайся, Сугане.
А!
Извините, Джо-сан!
Гатчамены выступили с заявлением
по поводу таинстенного пришельца,
появившегося в городе Нагаока,
префектура Ниигата!
Мы установили, что Гелсадра -
это безвредная, мирная форма жизни!
Напротив, на планетах, посещённых Садрой,
прекращались беспорядки, такие как унижение, преступления, войны—
Прямой эфир из Гатчанала
Эй, не носитесь перед камерой!
Эм... войны, бедность и прочее,
и некоторые из них докаладывали
о достижении мира на всей планете!
О, это Пай-Пай.
Для тебя я Пай-Пай-сан.
Прямой эфир из Гатчанала
Конечно, мы продолжим наблюдать за ней,
но мы всерьёз надеемся, что Гелсадра докажет
свою пригодность для роли спасителя Земли
под нашим пристальным надзором!
What's a savior?
Someone who'll save this planet!
But in order for this planet
to achieve true peace...
we need
your help.
Pai-Pai
That's why I created Pai-Pai Daycare
Center for the future of this planet...
Live from Gatchannel
Bite and Build!
Hey! Stop it!
Info-Live: The Millione Show
The Millione Show!
Hello!
Welcome to Info-Live: The Millione Show!
Well, yesterday was quite the surprise!
A new Gatchaman was born
right before the camera!
And that tall JJ guy just came,
Bam! out of nowhere!
I was shocked, too!
Celebration!! A New Gatchaman Member Is Born!!
A Nagaoka Girl in High School: "Whoa, me?!"
J stands out too much!
So, this newest member—
Misudachi Tsubasa-chan?
They're going to have a send-off
party for her at Riverside Senshuu.
The Millione Show will have
an exclusive live broadcast!
Oh, this will be exciting!
A savior? Seriously?
It's great if we only had
light topics like this,
Isn't Tsubasa-chan cute?
She makes that sound.
but before we get into that...
let's talk about the terrorist group,
VAPE, who's all over the news these days!
Today, we'll dig deep into the true
identity of this fearsome group!
Okay, here's what's up!
In-Depth Analysis!
What's VAPE?
The Red CROWDS Organization
In-Depth Analysis!
What's VAPE?
Yes, okay.
The Red CROWDS Organization
Until now, CROWDS were only blue--why red now?
What are CROWDS, anyway?
Materialized Human Consciousness
They can materialize their consciousness anywhere in an instant
The users' thoughts appear on their faces, that look like a fuzzy LCD monitor
Use with extreme caution!
Their consciousness? That's so hard!
OD, is this right?
Totally!
So in other words, CROWDS are
our thoughts and emotions given form.
Even children and the elderly
can use their smart phones
to send their consciousness
to a distant location.
It is true that CROWDS
have been very helpful
in removing debris after
the disaster and in volunteer work.
But on the other hand, they've given rise
to a dangerous organization like VAPE!
And the one who's promoting the use
of CROWDS as something anyone can do is...
Him!
Sugayama-san, is this really okay?
Won't something terrible happen eventually?
X, what's the reaction on GALAX?
Chaotic as usual.
Critiques of CROWDS and Rui
are growing by the day.
Between the VAPE attack
on the Prime Minister and now,
53,684 users have uninstalled the CROWDS app.
What about the mastermind
behind the red CROWDS?
Unfortunately, I have yet
to identify who that is.
It's nice to meet you, Ninomiya Rui-kun.
Who are you?
I am the one you most wish to see.
You were able to come here using CROWDS.
That means...
I oversee VAPE.
Celebrate: The Newest Gatchaman Member!
Misudachi Tsubasa
Good luck, Star of Nagaoka!
Let's welcome them now!
Misudachi Tsubasa-chan,
the newest member of the Gatchaman!
Ichinose Hajime-san, a Gatchaman!
Gelsadra-kun, our special guest!
Tsubasa!
Gel-chan's so cute!
It's Hajime-chan in the flesh!
Look this way!
She's blushing!
Hello!
I'm Misudachi Tsubasa!
We know!
Tsubasa!
Good Luck, Tsubasa!
Senpai!
Thanks!
Gatcha!
Starting with "Gatcha!"
right off the bat, huh?
Tsubasa-chan, let's get right down to it.
How do you feel now that you're a Gatchaman,
and what are your aspirations?
Okay!
Um... I became a Gatchaman
really suddenly yesterday,
and it still hasn't really sunk in.
It's really weird.
For now, I'm clueless
about all this hero stuff
and alien stuff to be honest,
but I'm going to give it my very best shot
and protect peace on Earth!
You're saying I'm wrong?
There is a critical difference
between you and I.
I had feared my power and sealed it away.
But you went ahead and used it right away.
Furthermore, you shared
that power with the general public.
What's so wrong about that?
Like I thought, you don't understand.
Understand what?
That the ones you gave this power to
are apes who will never evolve.
It means you are foolish for giving
such a dangerous plaything
to apes without any consideration.
I'm not foolish.
You're the ones who are
using dangerous powers.
That is all because of you.
We are only trying to stop
your idiotic actions,
We are trying to make the apes understand
just how dangerous it is to use CROWDS.
How foolish.
It's not. It is all for the sake of peace.
Peace?
You have no right to champion that word.
You have a big misunderstanding.
We are not the ones
threatening this nation's peace.
It is you, who gave his trust
to the idiotic apes.
Cut the bullshit!
We're not apes.
We are evolving, little by little.
I'll never take the CROWDS away!
I believe in everyone!
Am I included among them?
Of course.
No matter what kind of person you might be,
I'll never...
Oh, my.
It seems we are quite the apes, as well.
Who are you?
I am a radical peace activist.
What's this?
Bubbles?
They seem to be everyone's feelings
that Gel-chan has made visible!
Feelings?!
So cute!
They're like speech bubbles in manga!
Then we can call them bubbles-sama!
Wow!
Well, let's welcome the two Gatchaman!
Today, we have a special treat:
they'll transform for us!
Tsubasa!
Let's go, Tsubasa-chan!
Got it!
Go, Bird!
Huh?
Why?
You're still Tsubasa!
Right.
Go!
Maybe you're a bit nervous?
Want to give it another try?
Okay!
Go, Bird!
Tsubasa-chan, you do it like this.
Like this?
Like this, and this!
Like this, and this?
I understand now...
Gatchaman have it really hard.
What?
But Tsubasa-chan,
you work hard,
so I think you can get this down!
Thank you, Gel-chan!
Kill the CROWDS.
What the?
Huh? No way...
I'm going for a bit!
Tsubasa-chan, please evacuate
the audience outside!
No, I'll go, too!
I'll be fine!
Senpai!
Rui, we have an emergency.
Red CROWDS have appeared at Riverside
Senshuu in Nagaoka City, Niigata Prefecture.
Hajime!
Be careful of their attacks!
Good luck, Hajime-chan!
I know, Pai-Pai!
Yeah! Party time!
Rizumin, go!
Hajime-tan, I wanna join in, too!
Katze-san, good night.
Meanie!
Sparkle!
Everyone, the emergency exit is this way!
Newbie, stay calm and
help evacuate everyone!
Got it!
Everyone, please calm down!
Those bastards!
Go, Bird!
Oh, c'mon!
Go!
Ugh!
We have a situation!
Isn't this bad?
Everyone's a hero, right?
Here we go!
Let's go!
What?
We have blue ones now?
Seriously?
Stop...
Everyone stop.
We have a battle between
the blue and red CROWDS!
It's like a war!
Uh, oh! You're all way too excited!
A war!
Hey, stop!
This is a civil war.
I always thought CROWDS were dangerous.
Rui, what would you like to do?
Rui?
Listen up, newbie!
You stay out of this, no matter what!
But...
Everyone, stop!
Why?
We were having such a great time.
Please stop!
Gel-chan!
How dare you!
Tsubasa-chan, no!
Ow...
Granny!
X, terminate all the accounts
of all CROWDS users currently on scene.
Understood.
Emergency termination
of username MiichanMama-san.
This Way For
The Exit
Emergency termination of GoKenji-san.
Huh? I can't use it anymore.
Why? We were the good guys.
The blue CROWDS are vanishing.
Only the blue ones are vanishing!
That's enough for today.
Good work, everyone.
The VAPE guys get along, huh?
I'm sorry, Granny.
It's all my fault.
I'm fine.
Jeez!
Give that newbie a good, long lecture!
This is your responsibility as her mentor!
Roger!
Granny, please take care.
I'm truly sorry!
Was she okay?
Yes, she just sprained her ankle.
I'm glad it wasn't serious!
Senpai?
What?
I'm sorry I didn't follow orders today!
Please discipline me.
Okay.
Thank you!
Huh?
The sunset's really pretty.
Senpai?
Okay, let's go home and eat kaki peanuts!
U-Um, Senpai!
I'm serious!
Me, too!
Senpai!
C'mon, Senpai!
Uh, so this and this...
Oh, I know!
Oh, and...
Misudachi Fireworks Company
Today was sad.
Yeah.
Everyone will be united some day.
Gel-chan...
You're right.
Let's keep going together, Gel-chan.
It's going to be okay.
Your dream will come true one day.
Gel-chan!
Rui, I have identified the VAPE leader.
Name: Suzuki Rizumu    Age: 21   Sex: Male
Affiliation: Tokyo University Faculty of Medicine
DOB: April 25, 1995
Blood Type: A    Height: 178cm
Notes: Born in Hamamatsu City, Shizuoka Prefecture.
Moved to US soon after birth due to his father's work. Lived in Bellevue, Washington until age 10.
Upon return, lived in grandmother's house in Hamamatsu and moved to Tokyo upon entering college.
Received top scores in national exams while in junior high and high school.
He is Suzuki Rizumu, age 21.
He is a medical student at Tokyo University.
Thank you, X.
We'll All Evolve. Together.
I'm going to end...
this idiotic dream...
right here.
Yuru-jii, I'm going to Tokyo today.
I'm going to work hard at being a Gatchaman.
I'll try to make the world
a more peaceful place.
You can't shoulder the weight of peace.
Don't slack.
Yes, sir.
Thank you!
Melon-pan Soft Serve Ice Cream Sandwich
A melon-pan soft serve ice cream
sandwich is super yummy!
Yes, yes?
Vote Here
Today is the Tachikawa City
mayoral elections day.
Smart phone votes can be submitted
between 7:00 AM and 8:00 PM.
Voting will open soon.
Oh, finally.
Tachikawa Mayoral Elections
1. Shimizu Nobuo
2. Sasai Shunsaku
3. Kai Kaya
4. Akahori Yuujirou
5. Matsumori Shinta
Whoa! This is fun.
Tsubasa-chan, my foot's fine. Don't worry.
You tried to protect us with your courage.
We're all proud of you.
Don't give in.
Take flight on big wings, okay?
Thanks, Granny!
I'll take flight!
Tsubasa-chan.
Yes?
I know how you feel.
Huh?
You were acting
before you knew it, right?
Yes.
I know.
That's what it means to be a hero.
Senpai...
I'm going to try my very best!
Thank you for having me!
Hey, good luck!
I'm cheering you on, Star of Nagaoka!
Star of Nagaoka!
We have initial reports of the Tachikawa
City mayoral election results.
The incumbent, Mayor Shimizu,
is expected to win.
The voting turnout was 89 percent.
Shimizu-san won!
The voting turnout is incredible.
Nice job, smart phone elections.
It feels like a game.
Maybe it's a great idea, after all.