They did it!
There's one Gatchaman,
Ninomiya Rui-san, and someone
we believe to be tied to VAPE.
The Gatchaman has reached
the top of a skyscraper in Shibuya!
Urgent News: Mr. Ninomiya Rui Bleeding!
Gatchaman vs. VAPE
We have reports that it's the
rookie, Misudachi Tsubasa-chan!
Go, Tsubasa-chan!
So he's their leader.
Cherry Blossom Vine!
Rui-senpai!
Out of the way!
Innocent Storm!
Oh! Who's that now?
Is he a new Gatchaman, too?
He's tearing through the red CROWDS!
Innocent Storm!
Gel-chan!
Let's save Rui-kun together!
Thank you!
Go, Gatchaman!
They're so cool!
Just look at their teamwork!
Nice!
Urgent News: The New Gatchaman is on a Roll!
Gatchaman vs. VAPE
Go!
Good job, team!
Why can't they all get along?
Get 'em!
I surrender.
My purpose has been more than met.
VAPE has lost!
The leader's been captured!
You lost!
Die, VAPE!
Get out of here!
Thanks to valiant action from one
of our commentators, Tsubasa-chan,
it appears the matter's been resolved!
Urgent News: VAPE Leader Arrested!
Cowardly Terrorist Attack on Shibuya Quelled!
We did it, everyone!
The VAPE leader has been
captured by Gatchaman!
Yeah!
Nice.
Shh!
Quiet, please.
Sorry!
And it seems Ninomiya Rui-san is alive.
Rui-kun!
Rui-senpai, everything's going to be all right.
We caught the VAPE leader!
Why...
Why did you... interfere?
Interfere?
I told you...
not to come.
What?!
How could I just do nothing?!
Rui-senpai?!
How is he, Utsutsu-chan?
Don't worry.
I won't let him die!
I saved him,
but he said I interfered.
Why'd he say that?
Looks like it all worked out in the end!
This road is temporarily closed
in order to remove debris.
It's not safe.
Please stay back.
Hang in there.
Hang in there...
We'll be broadcasting live from
the Prime Minister's residence
about the CROWDS upheaval in Shibuya.
This is so sad.
This planet's in more
disarray than I'd thought.
There'd be no conflict
if everyone becomes united.
Is conflict so bad?
What?
What are you saying, Senpai?
Of course it's bad!
Isn't it sometimes necessary?
Are you saying it's okay
for people to get hurt?
No, but when people aren't united,
there can be pretty sparkles when they clash!
Huh?
I don't really get what you mean.
Don't mind her.
She sometimes says stuff that makes no sense.
It does make sense!
By the way, newbie.
I believe I told you to be on standby.
You shouldn't disobey orders.
I apologize for not following orders.
But I don't think I did anything wrong!
What?!
I couldn't let Rui-senpai die!
There's nothing more important than life!
Is that true?
Huh?
Is there nothing more important than life?
Of course not!
Heroes should protect life above all else!
But you don't know if Rui-kun thinks that.
Then are you saying I should've
just let Rui-senpai die?
That's not what I mean,
but I think it would've been
okay to give Rui-kun more time.
But Rui-senpai was hurt really bad!
I couldn't just watch and do nothing!
You've said things like
how conflict's necessary
and how Rui-senpai shouldn't
have been helped.
You're cold, Hajime-senpai.
Am I?
Am I cold?
"There's nothing more important than life."
That's a good motto for the Gatchaman.
We're supposed to love peace.
But you shouldn't disobey orders.
Heroes need to be flexible.
It's a matter of degree.
Hey, the newbie is learning
all this from watching you.
Prime Minister Sugayama has begun
an emergency press conference.
We're broadcasting live from
the prime minister's residence.
Regarding the red CROWDS disturbance
in Shibuya earlier today,
we have something to share with our citizens.
The red CROWDS, controlled by
the criminal organization VAPE,
were the sole perpetrators
in the terrorist incident
targeting the Prime Minister's plane.
We arrested the leader
of that organization today.
CROWDS have made major
contributions to various sectors
in terms of labor, medical assistance,
and social work.
I would like to support CROWDS'
continued presence in our society.
This is Smile TV.
So are you saying that the blue CROWDS
would never instigate a similar
incident in the future?
The blue CROWDS are under
X's absolute supervision.
They would never give rise to similar violence.
I'm your proof.
Just look at me.
Who can say that
Ninomiya Rui, who oversees X,
won't end up like me?
CROWDS have made major contributions
to various sectors...
CROWDS scary!
I would like to support CROWDS'
continued presence in our society.
I can't trust the blues anymore, either!
Do we really need CROWDS?
The Millione Show!
Hello. In today's Millione Show,
we'll start with this topic:
CROWDS terrorism in Shibuya!
The new Gatchaman and
a mysterious hero save the day!
I see!
So the mysterious hero who
fought alongside Tsubasa-chan
was Gelsadra-kun!
Yes, that's right.
I have to thank you for all of Japan.
Thanks to you, the terrorists were quelled,
and Suzuki Rizumu, who's suspected
of being their leader, was arrested.
Tsubasa-chan and Gelsadra-kun,
you're both new heroes who'll protect Japan.
Thank you!
I'll continue to do my best!
We've received a ton of questions about
you two ever since our broadcast yesterday.
You're viewed favorably on-line, too.
This must mean that our citizens
have acknowledged your worth.
I just wanted to take
everyone's sadness away.
You're so modest!
So, what's become a prominent issue is this!
Urgent Debate: Are CROWDS Safe?
Can We Trust the Blue CROWDS?!
We now know that once
CROWDS get out of control,
they can cause incidents of this magnitude.
Don't you think this strikes
some fear into people's hearts?
Huh?
Wait a minute,
the ones behind the incident
are the red CROWDS.
They're different from
the blue CROWDS, you know.
Sure, that's what Prime
Minister Sugayama said, too.
But we're discussing whether
the CROWDS are as safe
as the Prime Minister says they are.
What do you two think?
I think they are dangerous.
If this is what can happen,
why push to keep using CROWDS?
Yeah.
I don't want scary things
like that to happen again.
This terrorist attack wouldn't
have happened in the first place
if there had been no CROWDS.
So there's rising criticism
of Prime Minister Sugayama for carelessly
pushing the adoption of CROWDS,
and of Mr. Ninomiya Rui for developing them.
Mr. Ninomiya Rui has been critically
injured during the attack.
He's currently hospitalized,
but everyone's waiting to hear what
he has to say after he recovers.
Hang in there...
Hang in there.
What Rui-rui did was suicide.
You should've just let him die.
Saying stuff like "I believe," like whatever.
You know why, Katze-san.
You know why Rui-kun did that.
Huh?
No way!
No clue!
He's just an idiot!
Lololol!
I'd like to unite everyone's hearts
and get rid of all conflict.
Yeah, I think that's a great idea.
Hajime-senpai said a lot of things,
but it's just sad when
people hurt each other.
Yeah.
That's why I want to know
what everyone thinks.
You can really know that?
Yep.
I got it!
Maybe it's time to cut OD from the show.
Toriyama Millio-sama
Oh, why?
Our ratings have shot up after
OD-san became a regular.
I'm talking about the future of the show.
If a... supporter is a program regular,
we might make a negative impression
on our viewers, you know?
I see. You're right.
Look ahead, will you?
If you don't,
we'd risk losing our longtime hold
on the top spot in our airtime.
Come in.
Oh! Gel-chan, Tsubasa-chan!
Thanks for coming today.
You two are so popular!
Please become our regulars!
Millio-san, I want you
to unite everyone's hearts.
Huh?
Everyone listens to what you have to say.
I think you'd be capable
of uniting everyone's hearts
and creating a world without conflict.
What are you talking about, Gel-chan?
You shouldn't ask Millio-san
to do something like that!
Why not?
It's what everyone wants.
They want a world without conflict,
where no one is sad.
You say really interesting things!
But I don't think I can.
I'm not cut out for the job.
Being the host of a daytime
TV show is the best I can do.
Really?
I'm sorry, Millio-san!
Gel-chan doesn't know that
much about Earth yet.
It's okay.
Toriyama Millio-sama
I don't understand...
Aliens sure are different from us.
Right? We should make them regulars.
I thought Millio-san could do it, though.
Unite everyone's hearts.
You're still hung up on that?
You can't ask Millio-san
to do things like that!
Then who should I ask?
Who?
Um, someone important?
Who's someone important?
Well... a politician, maybe?
A politician?
Like Prime Minister Sugayama?
Guys, we have an emergency!
Prime Minister Sugayama
just announced his resignation!
Like I said, I'd like
to resign as prime minister
and nominate myself as a candidate for
the popular Prime Minister election to follow.
I'd like to stake my re-election
on what all Japanese citizens
believe the CROWDS to be worth.
If you truly believe CROWDS
are not necessary in society,
let me lose the election!
I'd like the people to vote!
Prime Minister Sugayama Resigns;
Puts CROWDS to the Popular Vote in the First Prime Minister Elections
Emergency Broadcast
There will be an election to choose the
next Prime Minister via smart phone vote,
as stipulated by legislation
passed last year.
Sugayama-chan is such a man.
What's the prime minister election?
Everyone will vote to decide who'll
be the leader of the government.
I don't think it's good strategy to put your
own neck on the line based on
what people think about CROWDS.
It isn't?
I don't think it's such a bad idea to put
the question to a general public vote
rather than just have CROWDS banned outright.
What a backwards planet this is,
to get in a scuffle about
something as minor as CROWDS.
How can children grow up
in safety on a planet like this?
The danger of CROWDS has become
known to the world at large.
Suzuki Rizumu did a good job.
No one can feel safe about
using CROWDS anymore.
I wonder about that.
It's like trying to ban all cars
just because someone lost
control of their car.
CROWDS are far more dangerous than cars.
They are tools humanity
was not prepared to use.
Man, this is why this planet will always
remain under protective surveillance.
There are people who are putting
it to good use to help others.
It's the rule of 2:6:2.
You're talking about how
in a group of people,
20% will be intelligent,
60% will be average,
and 20% will be foolish
as a general rule, right?
Right now, only 20% are able
to use CROWDS as intended.
When the average 60% becomes capable
of using CROWDS at that level,
that's when we can say CROWDS
are being used as intended.
But it's quite possible
that CROWDS will become
a destructive force in society
before that ever happens.
Um!
Am I part of the 20% or the 60%?
You're talking all high and mighty like that,
but is it that fun to look down on
people and classify them that way?
No, Tsubasa-chan, it's not about having fun.
Is this something we Gatchaman
should be even talking about?
We're heroes,
so isn't it more important that
we focus on helping people in need?
Well said, Tsubasa-chan.
This is what I meant by
clashing and sparkles!
Huh?
Lately, people are all "meh,"
but you're "bam!" You know?
That's why we need you right now.
I don't really understand what you mean,
but is this what we should
be really thinking about?
I don't know if we should be,
but I find myself thinking about it!
Yes, hello?
No, it's fine.
Okay, I'll go over when I can.
Leader, may I go somewhere for a bit?
Hm?
Well, we finished our debrief,
and we have no particular
plan to sortie at the moment.
You have my permission.
Thank you! Excuse me!
Where are you going, Tsubasa-chan?
Nowhere special. Want to come?
Yeah.
I got to know some of the
neighborhood association people
yesterday after the attack.
They said they were going to be clearing
debris today, so I thought I'd chip in.
Great!
I'll help, too!
Oh, Tsubasa-chan!
Hi, everyone!
You must be Gel-chan.
Thanks, you two! What a big help.
C'mon, guys! We have friends!
You should've invited
Hajime-chan and the others, too.
It'd get done faster if everyone chipped in.
I just thought they might say it's
not something Gatchaman should do.
Everyone's thinking too much.
Yeah, you're right!
Why do heroes need to think about 2s and 6s
Authorized
Personnel
Only
and categorize people into groups?
I don't like it.
If everyone united their hearts
and tackled problems together,
they'd be able to solve anything.
You're exactly right!
I get what you're saying
so much more than the others.
Tsubasa-chan, who are you voting for?
Huh?
Oh, you mean for the
prime minister elections?
Wouldn't you end up voting for Sugayama?
You think so?
What do you think, Tsubasa-chan?
I know it's not the best way to go about it,
but I don't really understand
the whole process,
so I'll just take a quick
look at election time
and vote for the one who looks good to me.
I guess it's like that.
It doesn't seem to matter who you vote for.
Maybe Sugayama's just the safe choice.
The Millione Show...
Info-Live: The Millione Show
Today, we have our semi-regulars,
Sadra-kun and Tsubasa-chan, with us!
Isn't it time you became real regulars?
Well, here's the first piece of news today!
Prime Minister Sugayama Resigns!
The First Popular Prime Minister Election Coming Up!
The first popular Prime Minister
elections will soon be held,
What Is the Popular Prime Minister Election?
Prime Minister Resigns -> Smart Phone Vote
but it's to be a smart phone vote.
Until now, Japan has been
an indirect democracy
where the most powerful man in government
Appointment by Diet Members -> Election by Japanese Citizens
would be appointed by
diet members we'd voted in.
But now, Japanese citizens
can vote for one themselves
with a tap on their smart phones!
Furthermore, there are no age or
nationality restrictions on candidates!
No Age/Nationality Restrictions for Candidates
Anyone can Nominate Themselves!
Anyone Can Register via smart phone
That's right!
By law, anyone... babies, grandpas, grandmas,
and even cat station masters and
aliens can become candidates!
Ha! He's dreaming.
As if an alien could be
voted in as prime minister.
You think so?
Of course!
An alien!
An alien prime minister!
Impossible!
Ridiculous!
Is it really?
Umm... So the prime minister
is the top leader of Japan?
That's right, Gel-chan.
It's an oversimplification,
but the prime minister basically gets
final say on what happens to Japan.
Can that person make
people's wishes come true?
Yeah.
They're the top gun of democracy,
so you could say that's their role.
Can that person stop everyone's conflict?
I'm sure they could.
Can that person put an end to sadness?
You're asking really tough questions.
Well, I guess the Prime Minister has the
most power to resolve everyone's problems.
Then I'll run in the
prime minister elections!
Huh?
That's way too fun!
Hmm... It may not be a bad idea!
Way fun!
But I don't think you can win.
Is that because I'm an alien?
No, because you're still a child.
Aliens would be fun.
But no one would think
that a child could do politics.
Gel-chan?
What a shock!
That's growing up way too much!
How's this?
Great!
Super great!
Yes, wonderful!
Thumbs up!
Impossible!
An alien as a prime minister candidate?!
No way! It's not possible!
Gel-chan's transformed again.
I don't think he needs
to change so many times, though.
Tsubasa-chan!
Y-Yes?
I want you to help me.
What?!
I think we can work together
to unite everyone's hearts.
Oh, okay! I'll help!
Yay!
Hey, Gel-chan!
Hajime-tan! He's gonna be a huge problem!
If you don't stop him now,
I'm gonna be in a huge pickle!
Help me, Hajime-tan!
Let's off him!
Let's off Sadra!
I'm gonna sleep.
Hey, don't ignore me.
Talk to me, you worthless bitch! Bitch! Bitch!
You shitty bitch!
Here!
If you tap that "yes,"
The First Popular Prime Minister Elections
Do you nominate yourself?
you become a candidate?
That's right.
Here, Gel-chan.
Do you wish to nominate
yourself as a candidate?
Yes!
Your application has been accepted.