Info-Live: The Millione Show
It's Info-Live: The Millione Show!
Hello!
Today, we have two guests
who represent the new era!
There will be Gelsadra-kun,
an alien from outer space
Alien
Gelsadra
Gatchaman
Misudachi Tsubasa
and Misudachi Tsubasa-chan,
a new Gatchaman.
Just look at those youthful smiles.
What's this?
I wasn't told of this!
Hey, Hajime!
Tsubasa-chan's so cute.
Listen to me!
Please show us!
So this is the much talked about...
This is everyone's feelings.
They seem to be calling
you Bubble-sama on-line.
Of course it'd be an alien who could
make that sort of thing happen!
Well, how is it, anyway?
How is Earth to you?
I'm kind of... disappointed.
Oh? Why's that?
I'd heard that Earth was blue...
but everyone...
...doesn't have a blue face!
Your face is too red!
Oh, it's too funny!
It's an alien joke.
Nice!
It's not an American joke,
but an alien joke!
Good, good!
Whew.
I would've been so embarrassed
if it hadn't gone over well.
My face would've turned bright red!
It already is!
You must've practiced this.
You could tell?
Whew!
Huh?
Here it comes!
The city
of teeming masses
is colored crimson
with determination.
A great wind will save
the flame of life.
The city with the teeming masses
is colored crimson with determination.
A great wind will save the flame of life.
Crimson...
So red, huh.
So this is the Gatchaman base!
Yep!
Tsubasa-chan!
Oh, Senpai!
Hey, newbie!
What was that TV appearance about?!
Oh, well, that's... uh...
Oh, are you talking about The Millione Show?
Then don't blame Tsubasa-chan.
Millio-chan begged her, didn't he?
Oh, excuse me.
I have another offer from Millio-san.
What?!
Tsubasa-chan!
Please come to The Millione Show live next week, too!
Oh, and bring Sadra-kun with you, of course!
They've both got it.
Got what?
Numbers, man. Numbers.
They're a hot item right now.
Let's make them semi-regulars.
You're not a TV celebrity!
You're one of the Gatchaman,
protectors of this planet!
Um, if I may,
I think there are people who'll
be encouraged if they see a hero!
We're here!
And we can protect them in times of need!
I think it's also a hero's responsibility
to reassure people like that!
Don't you agree?
You don't hold back, do you?
Leader!
"Leader"?!
Hey, Hajime!
She's a good girl!
I know!
Um, Leader.
What, newbie?
What's going to happen to Gel-chan?
Don't worry.
The protection and observation
of extraterrestrial life forms
are some of our duties.
We will not cause her discomfort.
Now that we've brought it up,
why don't we let Tsubasa-chan handle
Sadra-kun's observation and care?
Sure!
You can count on me!
Allow me to introduce myself again.
I am Misudachi Tsubasa, a first-year
in Nagaoka City Tokiwa High School.
I still have a lot to learn,
but I'm honored to be here!
I'm Gelsadra.
You already know me, Hajime,
OD, and Utsutsu, right?
Yes!
Utsutsu-senpai, nice to meet you again!
I'm gloomy...
Those three, you're meeting
for the first time.
First, that's Hibiki Jou.
Hi, Miss.
That's Tachibana Sugane.
Nice to meet you, Tsubasa-chan.
Nice to meet you, too.
And last but not least, this is Ninomiya
Rui, who joined right before you.
You're much girlier than me!
Nice to meet you.
That'll be all!
Oh, there's one more person.
You don't need to introduce him!
Here's the upstart!
I wants a story where the
innocent country bumpkin
gets corrupted by the city!
Wh-Where's that voice coming from?
It's Katze-san.
Berg-Katze?
Oh, you know him, Gel-chan?
Yeah.
He's very famous.
You're such a simpleton, Geruru!
"This is everyone's feelings"—
You're dreamin—
Katze-san's in me.
I see.
I don't really get it...
but pleased to meet you all!
Why don't we use this opportunity
to throw a welcome party?
Oh, but I guess Tsubasa-chan can't drink yet.
Sugane, now's not the time for that!
Sorry, Jou-san!
Are you going to ignore JJ's prophecy?
Are you talking about this?
The city
of teeming masses
is colored crimson
with determination.
A great wind will save
the flame of life.
Indeed.
JJ's words guide our actions.
The "flame of life"?
A "great wind"?
JJ is way too vague, as usual.
Crimson refers to red, right?
I have some ideas about that.
If we're talking red...
we're talking about CROWDS.
VAPE, the organization
controlling the red CROWDS.
During their previous attack on Nagaoka,
a man identifying himself as their
leader showed up in front of Rui.
Yes, he said to me
that they were violent pacifists...
Violent... pacifists...
How interesting!
Now's not the time to be
finding them interesting.
Why would pacifists
do such horrible things?
To wipe CROWDS out from the world.
They're intentionally
causing havoc with CROWDS
so that people would realize
the threat CROWDS pose.
Huh? But isn't it just the red
CROWDS who are dangerous?
Not necessarily.
There were some reports of pranks
and crimes committed by blue CROWDS.
X just took care of them before
things got too out of hand,
so they never received
much attention. That's all!
I see.
In the end, humanity wasn't
ready for the CROWDS ability.
I disagree.
Unfortunately, there are people
who use CROWDS for crime.
But nothing goes well on the first try.
We should move forward,
even if we have to fail several times.
You're welcome to believe in evolution,
but what if society collapses
before that happens?
It's not like we have
all the time in the world.
I don't think updating the world
will take that much time.
The VAPE leader is a self-driven
man in the extreme.
He has taken a wrong turn,
but he's very principled.
If there were more people
like him who could direct
their energy on the right path...
If there were, huh?
You're being idealistic.
What's the point of having
a world without ideals?
What do you think, Miss?
Huh? Me?
I just want to become a hero
who can protect everyone.
I'll try my best to do that!
Yeah!
The newbie is far more realistic.
Room 103 will be for the two of you.
Okay! Thank you.
You must be tired from the long trip.
Your beds are ready,
so you should go to sleep early.
Rui-senpai, you're really nice!
What's wrong?
Oh, I was just thinking that you and Jou-san
must have a similar sense of justice.
Katze-san?
Hello, Katze-san?
Silence...
If the VAPE leader can control CROWDS,
that means he's had his NOTE extracted,
just like Rui-kun's was, right?
Silence...
The only one I know who can
do that is you, Katze-san,
but is that true?
Hello, Katze-san?
Katze-san?
Fine!
And here I was enjoying my relaxation!
Fine, fine, fine!
I was the one who extracted Rizumin's NOTE,
but so what?
You've got a problem with that, dumbass?!
What kind of person is he?
The VAPE leader?
Well, you could say he's serious!
Totes serious!
But those types are the worst
when they snap, ya know?
Well, let's begin, shall we?
This is...
It's VAPE!
[Live Broadcast] Crisis in Shibuya! Red CROWDS Rioting!
So that's what this is about...
Got it.
Urgent News: Panic in Shibuya!
Red CROWDS Appear en Masse--City Turns Scarlet!
Shibuya, Tokyo
Are you seeing this, viewers?!
The entire city of Shibuya is scarlet!
I've never seen such a thing!
What's this?!
Are they hostages?!
Several citizens appear to be
restrained by the red CROWDS!
Oh, look! Blue CROWDS!
Don't underestimate us,
red CROWDS!
It's not working!
They're powerless!
Their organization is
almost organized military.
The blue CROWDS have no organization.
They don't stand a chance.
Let's do this!
We Gatchaman are the ones
who protect the planet!
Go, Bird!
Listen up!
There can be no casualties!
One, two!
Gatcha!
The Gatchaman!
The Gatchaman have come!
Why can't I fight?
But you can't even
transform at will yet, right?
Wouldn't you just hold everyone back?
Well...
Sonic Demon Blade!
Storm!
Flame Feather!
Fight until this life of mine
is extinguished, my shards.
Roger.
Bite and Build!
The Right Arm of Death!
Petites Ciseaux!
Blanc et Noir!
Digitize!
Caller ID Blocked
Hello, Ninomiya Rui-kun.
This is Suzuki Rizumu, isn't it?
Ninomiya Rui, hand over your NOTE.
I can't do that!
I see.
Then people will die.
Until now, we have kept human
casualties to a minimum.
That will end today.
Are you going to abandon them?
Are you going to avert your gaze
again from the lives that were lost
and continue to only preach
the utility of CROWDS?
Just like you did for
the Tachikawa Incident?
I'm sure you had noticed,
that in the shadows of your victory,
there were those who fell victim to CROWDS.
Enjoy your isolation,
Ninomiya Rui-kun, you foolish idealist.
Hajime-chan, I'm leaving this to you!
I'll go, too!
That's Ninomiya Rui-san!
Who's that before him?
Is he one of the VAPE members?
Why do you reject CROWDS so much?
Monkeys don't deserve such power.
In time, CROWDS will just
become a means for violence
for monkeys are easily
swayed by public opinion.
That's not true!
People can change!
Two to six to two.
Only a handful can change.
You know that in your heart.
No!
I believe each and every
one of us can evolve!
To update the world, we need—
You should stop with the idealism.
You just don't want to lose CROWDS.
To me, you look like a spoiled child
who doesn't want his
CROWDS toy taken from him.
Out, Bird.
Oh!
Ninomiya Rui-san has transformed back.
What are you trying to pull, Rui?
You may be right in that
I'm fixated on the idea of CROWDS.
But
I'm holding fast to my hope.
I want to believe in everyone!
You asked me, too,
if I also believe in you.
Yeah.
I believe in you...
that you are a man who
is driven by the right principles.
Ninomiya Rui-kun,
you're so...
so... foolish.
Oh, he collapsed!
Rui-senpai!
Ninomiya Rui-san just collapsed,
with blood coming out of his mouth!
There's so much blood!
Someone call the ambulance! Hurry!
I can't stand to watch this!
What are the other Gatchaman doing?!
Rui-kun, we're coming!
No!
Don't come!
Rui-san's getting up!
Fight! Fight!
This... is my fight.
I'm not going to lose!
I'll believe in him until the very end...
You idiot!
Now isn't a time for that!
Go, Jou-san!
I'll hold—
Sugane?!
I won't be what kills you.
It'll be your foolish ideals.
Rui-rui blood-fest, yeah!
Go, Rizumin!
So, so yummy!
Katze-san, shut up.
Urgent News: Mr. Ninomiya Rui Bleeding!
Gatchaman vs. VAPE
How could he?
He'll pay for this!
No, Tsubasa-chan.
Hold it in.
What's going on?
This needs to stop!
Someone!
Someone do something!
I'll go!
Wait.
What good are we if we don't go now?
I thought Gatchaman are
heroes who protect everyone!
You're right.
It's our mission to protect people's lives.
But Tsubasa-chan,
people have principles
that can't be sacrificed,
even if it means losing their lives.
Rui-kun's fighting that fight right now.
Would you still go?
Of course!
I see.
Tsubasa-chan!
No...
I can't stand this
Please help him
Someone do something
Screw you, VAPE
Rui-kun's gonna die!
This is too horrible
What's the gov't doing?
I don't want this!
Senpai!
Tsubasa-chan, watch out!
Please get out of the way!
Tsubasa-chan!
What the hell?!
If we can't help people in need,
how can we call ourselves heroes?!
Hundred Fireworks!
Oh, I see now!
If that's what everyone wants...
we'll become heroes!
Innocent Storm!
Stay away!
Take flight,
wings of hope!