So, it's finally elections season.
It'll be an historic first
prime minister elections by
smart phone vote on the GALAX platform.
Who will the Japanese people choose?
What the polls have shown today is this:
The Smartphone Prime Minister Elections Have Begun:
What Will the People Decide?
Sugayama Seitarou (73%)
Kuroiwa Dansaku (13%)
Yoshikawa Yuuki (8%)
Other (6%)
The incumbent, Prime Minister Sugayama,
is crushing the competition.
He holds more than 70 percent of the votes.
Suga-yan's way too strong!
But these are just poll results.
We still have a week
until the actual elections.
All the candidates still have a chance.
The one I'm particularly intrigued by...
is this one! Gelsadra-kun.
Gelsadra
Projected Votes: 1.9%
He's the first alien prime
minister candidate in history.
And he's going to be coming
by our show later on!
Tell me...
your...
desires!
I see...
I get it now!
Oh, I believe he's here!
It's unusual for Leader
and Utsutsu not to be around.
Allow me to introduce
to you our semi-regulars,
who, despite having super busy schedules
during election campaign season,
Pai-pai said something about standing
up for the future and left.
What's that about?
are still coming today—
TV Exclusive: The first alien candidate in history, Mr. Sadra!
Why did he decide to run in the prime minister elections?
Gelsadra-kun and Tsubasa-chan!
Alien
Gelsadra
Hello!
Gatchaman
Misudachi Tsubasa
Hello!
Well, Sadra-kun,
how confident do you feel about
the prime minister elections?
TV Exclusive: The First Alien Candidate in History, Mr. Sadra!
Why Did He Decide to Run in the Prime Minister Elections?
There's something I'd like
to tell the viewers today.
It's what I can promise you
if I become the prime minister.
Oh, that's what they call
the manifest, right?
What's yours?
Please tell the camera. Go on!
If I become the prime minister,
I'll abolish CROWDS.
Are CROWDS in big trouble?
Children are our most important treasure!
If I become prime minister,
I will direct my efforts to improving
childcare and parent support services.
Please Vote for Paiman,
Gatchaman Leader!
Please vote.
It's the Gatchaman panda.
Wow! It's really moving.
Look how popular I am.
I've already won the first
alien prime minister's seat.
I'm going to be so busy!
I'm gloomy...
Paiman
Oh, this is the perfect time to make
use of the politician's secretary!
Come help. Urgent.
This is an order.
I refuse.
Rui-senpai, what'd you
want to talk to us about?
More importantly, are you recovering okay?
Take it easy.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
But I can't just lie around in bed.
Gelsadra-kun, why would you abolish CROWDS?
I'm just listening to what everyone wants.
If I grant their wish,
they'll all be happy, right?
Their wish is temporary.
They're just afraid right now.
If they rely on others,
they'll never develop self-motivation.
Is this "self-motivation" really necessary?
Sorry. What you're talking about is too
difficult for me to understand a whole lot.
Can't the world be more simple?
Help those in need.
Protect those who are suffering.
Isn't doing that sort of thing
what we're about as Gatchaman?
Tsubasa-chan, the world won't
update if we only do that.
What people want isn't an updated world!
That's...
See, I told you.
That's enough, Rui.
I agree with abolishing CROWDS, as well.
That's why I decided
to help his election campaign.
What?!
I figured you might need a mastermind.
Yes, please!
Thank you.
This is getting pretty complicated.
What are you going to do, Hajime-chan?
I'm not sure.
It's ready, Sugane-kun.
Isn't this burnt?
I asked for it to be rare.
Forest Cafe Garden
Hey, did you decide
who you'll be voting for?
Sugayama-san, right?
Who else is there?
Right?
You know I'm supporting
Prime Minister Sugayama, right?
If you're going to support Gelsadra-kun,
it means you'll be supporting the opposition.
That's correct.
You are my secretary,
but your thoughts are your own.
Can I ask you something?
Is your goal still to achieve world peace?
Yes.
Then I have nothing more to say.
There's only one of me in this room.
I have a plan.
Let's begin.
PR Strategy for the Prime Minister Elections
~How to get Sadra elected~
Our biggest enemy is
Prime Minister Sugayama.
But the widespread support
he enjoys in the polls isn't real.
His approval ratings continue to fall.
So why would everyone vote for Sugayama-san
even if his approval ratings are sliding?
They don't feel other choices are viable.
Above all, that's the
prevailing mood right now.
The mood...
Changing their vote requires decision-making.
But they're not seeing
a compelling alternative.
In the end, they're just
going with the flow.
They just have a vague sense that
they can live with the status quo.
Vague...
Yeah, that's how I might
be making my choices, too.
That's the reality of this country.
But that's why...
you have a chance to turn things around.
Oh, it's Hajime-chan!
Really?!
H-Hello.
Can I shake your hand?
Sure.
Hey, who are you going
to vote for in the elections?
It's a secret.
Huh?
Because it's an election.
Alien Candidate
Gelsadra
Hello!
I'm Gelsadra. I decided to run
for prime minister in the elections.
I'm his cheerleader, Misudachi Tsubasa!
It's that alien.
Sadra-chan.
The girl next to him was amazing in Shibuya.
She's a Gatchaman, right?
I was little when I arrived on this planet,
but thanks to milk, I grew a ton!
Yeah, right!
Oh, excuse me.
I can carry that.
Where do you live?
Oh, can you?
Aren't you working?
It's fine!
It's part of a hero's job
to help people in need!
Especially now that there are more
efficient means of communication,
people look more favorably upon face-to-face
communication, even if it's inefficient.
What will determine the election results
are neither CROWDS or political ideals.
It'll be the mood of the people.
We might be facing a head wind right now,
but even the smallest opportunity
can turn things around.
It's an act.
It's fake. Creepy.
But they're helping people. I respect that.
Sugayama's the best.
Can't there be someone else?
Please vote for Sugayama Seitarou.
I thank you for your support.
Good job, sir.
Okay.
I hear the polls place you
at over 60% approval ratings.
It'll be an easy win.
It's been slowly sliding, though.
I'm getting a lot of these, too.
I'll never vote for you.
Anti-CROWDS
I hope you lose.
Who bothers saying "lose"? What's the point?
It's not productive, y'know?
I wonder if they're dumb.
What?
The camera was still rolling...
Huh?
Did he say "dumb"?
Who does he think he is?
Rui, we have a situation.
What's the matter, X?
Who does he think he is?!
I'll never vote for you, bastard!
You looked like an idiot on camera!
Crap!
Shame!: Mr. Sugayama's Clueless in More Ways than One
Instead of "luxurious," he said...?
This is footage of Mr. Sugayama visiting
a new urban nursing home last month.
Wow!
It's luxorous.
I'd consider living here myself someday.
Did you hear that?
He said, "luxorous."
Luxorous!
There's no such word!
The correct term is luxurious.
So embarrassing!
The leader of a nation, being unable
to use even a word like that—
considering the snafu on-screen last month,
I don't blame people for thinking
he doesn't deserve to be prime minister.
Oh, that's a bit harsh.
Switch Segment
Switch to the live broadcast!
Historic First!
The alien prime minister candidate, Gelsadra-kun
Hello, we're broadcasting from Riverside
Senshu in Nagaoka City, Niigata Prefecture.
We have a wonderful guest with us today!
I want to unite everyone's hearts.
Once united, we'll have no need
for a power that enables fighting!
Shhh. No.
Hush now.
You don't have to hush her.
No one thinks she's being noisy.
It's good that she's so healthy.
Good. That's the way to go.
That's... the way to go...
How wonderful!
That wasn't easy to say, I'm sure.
It speaks to the kind of person Sadra-kun
and his supporter, Tsubasa-chan, are.
So, their efforts as they continue
their brave trek across Japan
appear to be swaying the people's hearts.
Take a look.
Sugayama Seitarou (30%)
Gelsadra (20%)
Yoshikawa Yuki (11%)
Kuroiwa Dansaku (9%)
Despite Prime Minister Sugayama's
overwhelming lead earlier,
it's fallen to 30 percent.
In contrast, Sadra-kun has steadily
increased his margin to 20 percent.
Paiman
Keep up the good fight, Sadra-kun!
If you promise to vote for me,
right now, I'll give you this stuffed animal!
Paiman-san?
Oh, Reika!
Great timing.
Do you want a stuffed animal?
Are you aware of the
Public Officers Election Act?
Hey, let go!
I'm the leader of the Gatchaman!
I'm gloomy...
Let go! Let go!
Showing His True Colors?!
Prime Minister Sugayama Refuses to Eat Soup Kitchen Meal for Homeless
That was because I'd just
eaten lunch. I was full.
Loser
Be considerate!
So that's why you see homeless
You should've eaten
Don't make excuses
What?!
Scandal!
3 Days after the Tachikawa Incident
Eating Luxury Beef Stew!
I can't?
I can't eat beef stew?!
Seriously? lolll
High roller!
Right after that tragedy...
He's a goner
He was an idiot from the start
Profiting off our taxes
I bet it's not sometimes!
It's a once-in-a-while-thing.
I don't eat it all the time.
Why do people have to obsess about this?!
3000 yen for lunch?
He's out of touch
He thinks he's better than the rest of us
My lunch was 300 yen (cry)
Scum
Who cares about a 3000-yen beef stew?!
Just look at him!
Now the truth comes out
Huh? What attitude
He's done for lol
Anti-Sugayama
NO!! To Re-electing Sugayama
Suga-yan's done for!
Did you know, Hajime-chan?
Primitives love to gang up on
someone as soon as you give them
the "go ahead" sign to attack!
Really?
"Oh, he's a baddie!"
"On him, guys!'
"On him!"
They're just typing that shit
in their rooms on their keyboards!
Is that how it is?
Oh, there's Hajime-chan again!
Everyone, thank you so much
for coming in this head!
Look!
Citizens Rush to Hear Mr. Sadra Speak!
Gel-chan is so cute!
I'm the alien, Gelsadra!
Tsubasa-chan is cute, too.
I'm running for the prime
minister's seat in this election!
We're about the same age, aren't we?
You're yesterday's news, Hajime-chan.
The reason a recent arrival to this planet
How do you feel right now?
Right now?
would want to become prime
minister is simple...
Everyone's the same color.
Oh, the election's tomorrow already.
You're right.
Did you all decide who you're voting for?
Well, Gel-chan probably.
Yeah.
Tomorrow's the vote.
Who are you gonna vote for?
Not Sugayama.
Yeah, who'd be suicidal like that?
My grandma said he was nice to her.
You're such pushovers lol
I'm okay giving him a try.
Seriously? lol He's an alien lol
This nation's finished lol
He's better than Sugayama.
I'm voting because Tsubasa-chan's cute.
Sadra's saying good stuff.
And he can win a real fight.
Rui, shall I delete negative articles
about former Prime Minister Sugayama?
No.
Doing it will only have the opposite effect.
But at this rate...
Jou-san...
Is your goal to become an ally
to a privileged kind of justice?
It's finally the elections tomorrow.
Thinking that made me nervous
and turned my face bright red.
That's how it's always been!
Lastly, I'd like a comment from my
staunchest supporter, Tsubasa-chan.
Umm... Thanks for coming out
in big numbers today.
Gel-chan has promised to end CROWDS.
I don't think we need CROWDS anymore, either.
Instead, I promise you
that in times of crisis,
the Gatchaman— I will come help!
That's what heroes do!
Gel-chan and I will always protect you!
Why aren't you happy?
You don't become the same
color as everyone else.
Always the weirdo.
You're the weirdo, Jou-san.
You're thinking this isn't what you wanted,
but you still try to keep it going.
It's not right.
It's not.
There was 188.
There were that many people injured
during the Shibuya terrorist attack.
That many people fell victim to CROWDS.
Above all...
one of us almost lost his life.
Elections are intended to have
each individual think for themselves
and choose the candidate they
want to entrust the future to.
This... having people choose with
the flow... is definitely wrong.
Yeah.
But still!
I can't let CROWDS roam free!
Even if the means are wrong,
this will achieve my justice!
I see.
Info-Live: The Millione Show
The Prime Minister Elections Voting Day Has Come!
The day has finally come!
It's the day of the fated smart phone
prime minister elections!
Who will stand at the helm of this nation?
First Prime Minister Elections
Candidate Sugayama Seitarou
Place Vote
Return to Selection Screen
Vote Accepted
Hi, Rui-kun.
Do you want to go together
to visit Rizumu-san?
Huh?
You hadn't finished your
conversation with him, right?
Amnesia Effect, huh?
I thought it might be you, Ninomiya Rui-kun.
I'm Ichinose Hajime!
Nice to meet you.
And this is...
Katze!
Been a while, Rizumin!
Is that you, Berg-Katze?
How you've changed.
You're a difficult one to understand.
The same goes for you, Rizumin.
Unlike Rui-rui, even though you didn't
budge one bit when I took out your NOTE,
you suddenly put on revolutionary airs!
Talk about a 180!
I never intended to use
the power you gave me...
until Rui-kun there rushed
to commit his foolish acts.
I don't think of myself as foolish.
You still delude yourself after that debacle?
You must know, deep down,
that this nation's full of apes
who are incapable of independent thought.
No, that's not true.
The rule of 2 to 6 to 2.
Who do the 60 percent follow in this nation?
That'd be public opinion.
Japan does not have a rational society—
only irrational, sordid public opinion.
That's why I call the masses apes.
Even in prison, I can watch
television at certain times.
The smart phone prime minister elections
are going to be interesting.
Interesting?
Why do you think former
Prime Minister Sugayama
is being subjected to that much criticism?
Do you think everyone's personally
aggrieved by his gaffes and mistakes?
Of course not.
Most of the people attacking
him are not angry.
Why are they criticizing him then?
Attacking him?
Because that's the prevailing
mood among the people.
There's no actual reason.
There's no need for rationale.
Just because that's how the wind blows,
they'll attack the same things
and like the same things as everyone else.
No.
You're being a radical.
No, that's the simple truth.
At least former Prime Minister Sugayama
is only being subjected to slander
and character defamation.
If it had been anyone who'd committed
a more serious offense...
The apes may well just say
it's how the wind blows
and lynch that person using CROWDS.
No.
What if their target was a group of people?
An entire village?
Another nation?
Without individual will, the apes may
be moved to destroy the entire world.
You're wrong!
I have a question.
What is it?
So you already know who'll win
this election, Rizumu-san?
Of course.
1-2-3!
Elections News Flash: Votes Being Tallied for the First Prime Minister Elections!
Will the Incumbent be Reelected, or Will We Have Our First Alien Prime Minister?!
Prime Minister Election Results Soon to Be Announced!
The worst thing possible for
this nation has appeared—
the master ape.
It seems we have the voting results.
Prime Minister Elections Midterm Poll Results
Sugayama Seitarou (30%)
Gelsadra (20%)
Sugayama Seitarou (14%)
(Winner) Gelsadra (68%)
Yay!
We did it!
Yay! This is amazing, Gel-chan!
An Alien Prime Minister is Born
It seems we are witnessing an historic moment!
We have the first alien prime
minister in the history of mankind!
He...
is dangerous.
Let's keep this up, Gel-chan!
Yeah!
Let's unite everyone!