Congratulations, Gel-chan!
Elected
I mean, Prime Minister Sadra!
Our quasi-regular is now a prime minister!
Well, what a feat! How wonderful!
Grandpa, they say he's an alien.
Let's take a look at how the city's doing after Prime Minister Sadra's election!
Well, why not?
This is the result of our direct vote.
I can just relate to him somehow, you know?
Even though he's an alien.
How strange.
Huh?
So Prime Minister Gelu-lu is born.
Go, Bird!
Man, I still can't do it!
Tsubasa-chan, weren't you able to transform during the VAPE thing earlier?
That time, I saw Rui-senpai being hurt,
and I just got so mad.
All the blood just rushed to my head.
I'd transformed before I knew it...
Then how do you feel now?
Huh?
Right now?
Well, I guess I feel normal.
Tsubasa-chan's not a Gatchaman yet.
You're still Tsubasa-chan!
Huh?
I'm me?
Isn't this diagram too bloated?
Huh?
Well, um...
About the defense budget,
why does it have to be so high?
Well, if I remember correctly, it's because...
I'll eradicate conflict from Japan!
And I'd like to make a nation where
people are united and full of smiles!
Are we going to solve
everything with military force?!
Akiyama-san, why do we
need to use military force?
Huh?
Oh, no.
I don't think military force is good, so... well...
Right!
Military force is never an option!
That's why I'm making my slogan
"Our Hearts as One!
Let's Create Our World Together!"
I'm going to move as speedily
as I can through political reform.
Alien!
Don't talk bullshit!
Yoshikawa-san, I am an alien,
so you're right about that!
But I never talk bullshit!
Huh?
U-Um, I suppose.
So, to get right to the point...
Hey! Try to transform!
Kishida-san!
What do you think?
Huh?
Well... W-Well done.
Thank you!
So, about this year's budget,
I'll remake it based on my new slogan!
Y-Your face is red!
Thank you for your opinion, Kashima-san!
Yes, my skin's been red
since the day I was born!
Is something wrong with that?
Okay, who's the next heckler?
Prime Minister Sadra!
How do you intend
to resolve the CROWDS problem?
I intend to reach a resolution
everyone can agree on.
I'll let you all know as soon as
preparations are made.
There are rumors that you
are in a romantic relationship
with Misudachi Tsubasa-chan, a Gatchaman.
A romantic relationship?
So... Are you two in love?
I like Tsubasa-chan a lot.
She's a really great person!
So, given how you're manly and all,
is your other manifesto also respectable?
Umm... What did you want to talk about?
Ah, right.
Everything is so new to you—
perhaps you're having a difficult time.
I have experience and connections.
I'll help you in any way I can.
Okay. Thank you.
They're all over the place?
Yes.
What the Diet members say is
very different from what they think.
I feel very uncomfortable.
They're reading the mood.
Reading the mood?
Yeah, they sense stupid things like the fact that you're new to politics
or that you're popular and
have a lot of push in the moment,
so then they badger you
or try to get on your good side.
I see.
Listen, Gel-kun.
Politicians aren't the ones
making this country what it is.
Everyone is.
Everyone?
Everyone!
I want to know more about
what everyone's thinking!
Gel-chan, I'll help, too!
Thank you.
Tsubasa-chan, the air's nice and fresh here.
Yep.
I kinda reminds me of Nagaoka.
Takamatsu.
Good morning, everyone.
Hi, everyone!
There's lot of space around me!
My face is red, and my hair is blue,
but I am a very decent alien!
I won't bite. Ever.
Let's work together to make
this as painless as possible!
Prime Minister Sadra,
you're commuting by train?
Yes!
Oh, you can call me Gel-chan.
Oh, if it isn't the Prime Minister!
What? Hey, alien!
What's big brass like you doin' here, eh?!
Oh, even I want to drink
until I pass out sometimes.
Also, my face is red,
but I'm still sober.
He's funny!
I like him.
Hey, Gelra!
There are too many politicians!
Hey, what's the salary for politicians?
They earn about twenty million on average.
Also, the Prime Minister
earns about forty million.
Wow!
You tax thief!
It's too high, right?
Please tell me what you think.
Oh, excuse me!
Please get this man
another round of draft beer,
and four ice creams on top of that.
Oh, it'd be our pleasure!
Okay, everyone smile!
I'm sad we're not all united.
Now we are.
You're right!
We're united!
Okay, here we go, everyone!
Gelu-lu!
You're not going home?
Isn't your family worried about you?
I don't have anyone at home at night.
I see.
Okay!
Let's play together!
Oh, wow!
Wow!
That's right!
We are really lacking childcare facilities
like kindergarten and preschool.
In some areas, they don't
even have the budget.
I see.
Leader, let's protect
the children's future together!
O-Okay!
You're doing good, Sadra.
I'm gloomy.
What do you think?
This is the best view on this island.
Are you okay?!
He's been like this recently.
Has he been to the hospital?
There are no doctors on this island.
We only get one doctor who comes here
once a month from the mainland.
Prime Minister Sadra!
You're making trips like this every day,
but for what purpose?
Hey, watch it!
Are you okay?
Hey!
Apologize to him!
Sorry.
It's all right.
It's good that you're
really invested in your job.
I'm really sorry.
It's all good.
Oh!
Since we're all here, let's have a professional photographer take a group photo!
Huh?
Sure.
Okay, everyone. Please get together!
Goodbye!
Tsubasa-chan, you're the kind of person who can make other people smile.
Huh?
Where's this coming from, Gel-chan?
Tsubasa-chan, I'd like to have
your support moving forward.
Let's make everyone's hearts into one.
Okay!
Okay, everyone.
Breathe in deep! Deep!
Oh, Sugane-kun's here!
Huh?
What's that?
What?!
You don't know?!
It's called the Gel sign.
See?
Oh, it's popular?
I see.
So you're back because
of work with Gel-chan.
That's tough.
You must be busy,
but do take care of yourself.
Got it!
Okay!
I just don't want to see
anyone feel sad anymore.
That's why I want to protect
peace for everyone with Gel-chan.
What's peace?
What?
What's peace to you?
Well...
I guess it'd be everyone
being united... and happy.
What does it mean to be united?
Are you and I united?
Of course.
You and I, our souls are connected.
No.
I'm me.
Yuru-jii!
Don't say such sad things!
So if our souls are connected,
we become united?
And there'd be peace?
Yeah!
If everyone can understand each other at that level and become one,
there will be no more conflict!
What if there are people
who don't think that way?
Then I'll just try harder until they do!
You know nothing.
That's not true!
We're fighting every day out there in a world you don't understand!
Don't throw that word around like you know what it means to fight.
What do you know?
You're just staring at
the shogi board every day!
I'm done.
Tsubasa, come back to Nagaoka.
What do you mean?
Yuru-jii, stop.
Tsubasa and Gel-chan
are working hard every day.
Working hard is enough?
That pardons everything else?
Stop it. You're just arguing
for the sake of argument.
Come home, Tsubasa.
No!
Then I won't teach you fireworks.
I don't care anymore!
Tsubasa-chan.
I'm gonna do this!
Just watch, Yuru-jii!
Tsubasa-chan?
Well, that made me feel a lot better.
Gel-chan, let's protect peace!
Okay!
What a surprise!
The new cabinet — is just Gel-chan!
Umm... Then what about the cabinet members?
I had all the politicians and officials resign
and work instead in jobs
appropriate to their specializations.
Er, then what about the National Diet?
Right, that's being renovated so that the citizens can make good use of it.
News? Huh?
Then where will the Diet sessions be held?
At Tachikawa City's Flower Green Park!
So you'd have it by yourself, Prime Minister?
No, it'll be me and everyone else!
I'd like everyone to freely comment.
Wow!
This is a revolution, right?
That's pretty good.
Extra! Extra!
The Sadra Cabinet is Just One Member!!
Only one politician! Wow!
"Prime Minister Slashes Own Salary Down
to Minimum Needed to Meet Living Costs."
Wow! What's this?!
Huh.
"Prime Minister to Disclose
All Daily Expenditures on GALAX."
Holy cow!
"Open Diet Session to Be
Broadcast Live from Park."
Maybe I'll make a comment.
"All Political Decisions to Be Made via Citizen
Smart Phone Vote in Remote Direct Participation."
So that means we can all decide?
That's very open of him.
This is a huge revolution
that'll go down in Japan's history!
But it's almost too revolutionary.
I hope he can handle
doing everything by himself.
But there was a lot
of money going toward paying
Diet members and
to manage Diet proceedings.
If this tax money can be
effectively repurposed, it'll be huge!
And think about all the elections.
I think each election
costs 60 billion yen.
Hmm?
What?!
Here are the results of the smart phone vote:
Click Here to Start Voting
Do you support the new
cabinet system and policies?
Click "Right!" if you support this,
Right!           No Way!
and "No Way!" if you don't.
If the vote indicates a majority dissent, Prime Minister Sadra will resign.
The smart phone vote
is getting started right away!
Not to mention, Gel-chan will resign
if there's a majority dissent!
Wow! He doesn't hold back.
You're too sportsman-like, Gel-chan!
I love it!
It sounds fun.
Let's see what happens first.
Great.
It's good.
Rui, the smart phone votes are in.
Right!
No Way!
Let's put today's agenda items
to a smart phone vote!
New legislation is being put to a smart phone vote, one after the other!
National pension payouts will be
National Pension Payouts: Doubled
doubled!
Sales Tax: 2%
Sales tax will be
decreased to two percent!
All services currently being
offered by government offices
Services Offered by Gov't Offices:
Available Online via GALAX
will become available via GALAX!
Vehicle\Liquor Tax: Decreased
Vehicle tax and liquor tax will
also be greatly reduced!
Furthermore, there will
now be government assistance
to childcare, hospice care,
and social services
for the elderly.
The number of facilities
and staff will be doubled,
and all services will be free!
Wow!
What's next?
Government assistance
for medical services
in isolated island
communities will be increased!
There will be initiatives
to recruit doctors from overseas, as well!
Come on, doctors worldwide!
Former officials who got
cushy jobs will get fired!
There will be no incentive
to collude with companies now.
You can train for a lot more job types now at the vocational training center! lolol
Wow!
Let's all aim for 0 percent unemployment!
It's not "pretty"?
Becoming united isn't?
Yeah. It's just not sparkly.
Really?
I don't think so.
Oh, I have a question!
Gel-chan, you said before that the bubbles were what people were thinking.
Yes.
What's yours look like?
Mine?
I've never seen yours.
I hope it's the same color as everyone else.
"I hope it's the same color as everyone else"?
He's annoying! Super annoying!
Oh, Katze-san, you're
all fired up today like usual.
Of course!
Hajime-san, you've trapped
Berg-Katze inside of you, right?
Huh? Yep!
Um, you're okay, right?
Hmm?
Gel-chan,
we're about to start!
Good morning!
This is footage taken this morning.
Our Hearts as One!
Our World for Us
to Create Together!
Maybe it's Gel-chan's influence,
but everyone's talking to each
other and enjoying their commute.
Hmm? What?
We were in the middle of a segment,
but it appears the Gel-Gel Live Diet Session
is finally making progress
on the CROWDS problem!
Now that you're all familiar
with the smart phone vote system,
I'd like all citizens to decide
whether CROWDS use
should become prohibited!
Please tell me your answer!
Sugane-kun!
Something's on Gatchannel!
Where's this?
Here's the Gay-chan!
Rui's condo right?
Seriously?
Nice digs lolol
Prohibiting CROWDS would also mean
rejecting our own species' evolution.
If we can coexist with CROWDS,
it would mean the nurturing
of our ability to trust in others
and our individual
motivation to take action.
It'll signify a big step for humanity.
CROWDS symbolize potential.
Why would we choose
to cut off our own future?
Do you believe CROWDS use
should continue to be allowed?
If you agree, click "Right!"
If you disagree, click "No Way!"
Right!           No Way!
CROWDS is so out now.
The city's in really good spirits lately.
Yeah.
Right!
Hey, Suzuki.
CROWDS prohibition has been
decided by smart phone vote.