What do you think, Kimura-san?
Nagaoka Fireworks Festival:
August 2-3, 2016
Misudachi Fireworks Company
Nagaoka Misudachi
All right!
On with the usual!
An evacuation advisory has been issued.
The rainfall over the past 24 hours
has exceeded what's typically expected
over the entire month this time of year.
Tanizaki City should remain on alert for
mudslides due to rain saturating the soil.
Next up is news on the continued problems
related to the CROWDS phenomenon...
Nationwide Damage from Red CROWDS Activity
Convenience Store in Saitama City
Yesterday saw more incidents
by red CROWDS nationwide.
Prime Minister Sugayama made a statement
It sounds like the whole world's
going to hell in a handbasket.
yesterday that their origins
are as of yet unknown—
Good morning!
Morning, Tsubasa.
Morning.
Tsubasa, Yuru-jii is already at it.
Going right over!
Relax, relax, relax, relax, relax...
Exhale properly!
Got it!
Relax, relax, relax, relax, relax...
You're doing it wrong!
I'm exhaling properly!
This is tough!
Don't complain.
Okay!
Hey, Yuru-jii.
Misudachi
When do I get to wear that, too?
You've got a ways to go.
Huh? Why?
UFO here
Don't slack.
No, Yuru-jii.
Look!
Run!
Thanks, Yuru-jii!
What's this?
Tsubasa!
Are you okay?
Oh, Kodama.
Yep, I'm fine.
She's okay, guys!
What is this?!
A UFO?
Oh, no!
And we just planted the rice!
It's an alien invasion!
Come save us, Gatchaman!
Ichinose Hajime
Incoming Call
"Ichinose Hajime"...?
The Ichinose Hajime?
It's Hajime-chan!
Nice to meet you!
I'm Ichinose Hajime, a Gatchaman!
I'm Tsubasa!
Nice to meet you!
Everything's going to be
okay now, Tsubasa-chan!
I'm so happy we met!
Nice to meet you!
Oh, it's Paiman!
Utsutsu-chan!
We've come here to Nagaoka
City in Niigata Prefecture
to place an extraterrestrial
life form under our protection!
This is so cute!
Oh...
Oh, is that your grandpa?
He's my great-grandfather.
I'm Hajime!
Nice to meet you!
Hello, Hajime-chan.
Hajime-chan, this way, please!
I'm gloomy...
Good luck, Gatchaman!
A UFO and the Gatchaman!
Mom!
Nagaoka City might become super famous!
My sock!
Okay, everyone! Stand back!
UFO!
I told you to stand back!
The alien might be dangerous!
Hajime, stay on guard!
Roger!
Go, Bird!
She transformed!
Alien-san!
Can you hear me?
What'd you come to this planet for?
Alien-san!
Please respond!
A-An alien?
What's up with the wind?
It looked this way!
Don't look into its eyes.
I'm scared of the alien...
Out, Bird!
So cute!
Oh, wow!
She hugged the alien!
Oh, it's her.
Huh? You know her, Pai-pai?
Don't call me that!
You're really so cute.
Oh, it's her.
What? You know her, too?
Huh?
What?
A delicate ray of light
falls upon a land illuminated by fireworks
near the North Sea...
Even JJ's losing his edge.
But this "delicate light"
business makes you worry.
JJ's prophecies are more
for reference than anything else.
How we choose to interpret and act on them
rests solely on us Gatchaman.
Wow! You're really starting
to sound like a leader.
Doesn't he, Katze-san?
Eh, he's just a panda!
Don't call me a panda, you pyromaniac!
It's coming this way.
I'm scared.
You don't need to be scared.
She's not dangerous.
Are you sure?
Mom!
It's only a little girl!
Good morning!
My name is Gelsadra!
Oh, wow!
It turned into a human!
I'm Hajime!
Nice to meet you!
Gel-chan, why did you come here?
Shh! Don't ask.
What's this wind?
Huh? What's this?
Gel-chan, what's this?
They're everyone's thoughts.
Something weird's floating there.
Mom, it's all floppy.
Where'd this come from?
What's this? Put it back.
How strange...
I'm gloomy...
Wow.
Everyone's so different. It's pretty.
Hajime-chan, you're amazing!
Amnesia, Remind!
What's that?
So pretty!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Look that way!
Gel-chan's cute.
She seems nice enough.
That's what I thought from the start!
Right!
Alien-san, are you here to sightsee today?
What'd you do, Gel-chan?
The atmosphere just got a lot better.
The atmosphere?
Huh?
Oh, um, the atmosphere...
Tsubasa!
Huh?
Oh, Gel-chan.
The atmosphere is...
It's on this planet,
and... well...
Anyway!
It was really fun when
everyone came together, right?
That's called a good atmosphere.
Yeah, see?
Good atmosphere!
Thank you, Tsubasa-chan.
You're welcome!
Welcome to Nagaoka.
So the rumors were true.
I'm gloomy.
Huh?
Mine doesn't change.
Of course yours wouldn't, Hajime-tan.
Why not?
Because you're you, Hajime-tan.
More importantly, just let me outta
here already, you shitty bitch!
Katze-san, shut up.
Late last night,
I have to say, I thought I was a real goner.
Prime Minister Sugayama's flight was
attacked by several red CROWDS.
Even the Prime Minister Targeted!
Tachikawa City, Tokyo Prefecture
VAPE, the Red CROWDS Organization
They use CROWDS, even though
they say they're anti-CROWDS.
I wonder what their goal is.
The mysterious group behind the attack
has identified itself as VAPE.
There have also been reports that JSDF
fighters were lost during the altercation,
I'm counting on you guys!!!
Please vote for Mayor Shimizu!!
It'll be the first smartphone election in history!
and we are seeking confirmation.
It's said that "VAPE" refers to "Violent Ape."
Aggressive monkeys, more or less.
Monkeys?
X, what does everyone think about CROWDS?
Status quo is fine (52%)
Should regulate (20%)
Should eradicate (18%)
Over the past week, those in favor
of the status quo fell 12 percent.
So now almost a half are revolutionaries.
I'm sure the earlier incident
from the day is a factor,
but talk about a rapid
shift in public opinion.
It wasn't so long ago
that everyone was happy
saying that CROWDS changed the world...
The Prime Minister's popularity
has also gone down.
Oh, man...
But I'm not the sole leader of this nation.
Everyone is.
And CROWDS support that notion.
They're our hope.
I believe in you all.
But, Prime Minister.
Not all people are the same.
What?
Because there are some monkeys among us,
this nation hasn't been able
to produce a civilized society.
That's harsh.
That's reality.
Our role is to grasp
reality with objectivity
and move people to action.
I see.
I guess becoming secretary
to the mayor has changed what you say.
No, nothing's changed.
My dream has always been, and always will be,
world peace.
That's the spirit!
Oh, The Millione Show is starting.
Hello!
OD's into it like usual.
Happy New Year!
The Millione Show
Gatchaman
Hello! How is everyone?
Good morning.
Sugane-kun!
I'll sit next to him!
Hey! Me first!
Me, me!
Please don't fight.
Okay!
Look at you, all happy and
gorgeous like usual, OD!
Aw, thanks.
Sugane-kun, you're so cute!
Please smile one more time!
Oh, jeez...
Don't be so small-minded! Be a man!
Small-Minded Celebrities!
Even *that* celeb hottie!?
Top 5 Closet Small-Minded Male Celebrities
D-san!
Good job today!
Tough love from you as usual, OD!
Oh, it's Millio!
Millio's fun.
Here comes the fairy!
Gross, gross, gross!
OD's quite the celebrity now.
Pai-pai, you're eating too much.
I heard D-san's got
three TV commercial deals.
I'm gloomy.
Yeesh.
Oh, come to think of it, I hear
there's someone around here
who's supposed to become a new Gatchaman.
Oh, really? Here in Nagaoka?
A delicate ray of light
falls upon a land illuminated by fireworks
near the North Sea
where it will meet wings
that are still blue...
What's your dream, Tsubasa-chan?
Huh? Me?
Well...
that's to become a fireworks craftsman.
Right, Yuru-jii?
A fireworks craftsman, huh?
That's great.
Yuru-jii is a super famous
fireworks craftsman.
He's even had a movie character based on him.
He made this giant Niagara fireworks, too.
Wow!
It's super gorgeous!
Yuru-jii is basically a god here
in Nagaoka, the fireworks capital.
Don't exaggerate.
Nagaoka Fireworks Festival   8/2-3 2016
The fireworks festival is on
the second and third of August!
You should all come see it!
This year's really special because
Yuru-jii's going to be a hundred years old!
A... A hundred years old?!
Wow.
I want to live that long, too.
A hundred? That's young.
Yuru-jii, do you play shogi?
Don't bother, it's boring to watch.
He never makes any moves.
It stays just like that for weeks.
I like things like that!
Hey, Yuru-jii.
Don't you think it's time
you teach me about fireworks?
Summer break just started today.
I can't leave the business to you.
That's mean. Why?
What am I missing?
That doesn't tell me anything!
But I think you'll make it.
What?
I want to cheer you on, Tsubasa-chan.
Gel-chan.
Having a dream is a wonderful thing.
Gel-chan,
you're so nice!
I'm cheering you on, too.
I don't want to let
this family tradition die out.
Well, it's only if Yuru-jii will allow it.
Just look at this footage!
We're all tired to death of seeing
them day in and day out...
It's nice to have hopes
and dreams as young'uns.
but it's the red CROWDS again!
Just what do they even what?
But just look at the world.
They're terrifying!
The mysterious organization known as VAPE
Cowardly Terrorists
Cut it out!
Red CROWDS on rampage again!
What Does the Violent CROWDS Group, VAPE, Want!?
is shaking the very
foundations of this nation!
Even the Prime Minister's life was in peril!
Who is their next target?
How long must we spend sleepless nights?
This is unconscionable!
Jeez, what are they doing?
There were elderly and children
running away in that footage!
This planet still needs to be under
protective observation for sure.
Right, right.
This is the act of cowards!
I can't believe they'd use
the CROWDS from far away
What's wrong, Gel-chan?
to attack the weak and vulnerable!
I don't want this.
That's right.
You have a young child yourself, right?
What?
Everyone's all over the place.
Yes, I do.
That makes me sad.
He's really scared.
I want everyone to be united.
I walk him to school and back every day now.
Are all parents doing that?
Of course. That's what I hear.
Right?
I see.
Right.
Gel-chan, you're so nice!
You're like an angel!
Did you hear that, guys?
She wants everyone to be united!
That's so impressive!
Yuru-jii, who's that?
My younger brother.
I see.
Jeez! Vape or Dape, I don't care!
They just need to cut it out!
Millio-chan, don't get too hotheaded.
Give us some cheerful news once in a while!
Leave that to me!
Let's have a change of pace
and hear a surprising piece of news!
Saitou-san!
Emergency
Live Broadcast!
An Alien Invasion in Nagaoka City, Niigata Prefecture?!
Hi, this is Saitou from Smiling TV.
A UFO just landed nearby,
and the whole area is in an uproar.
Huh?
I've seen this house somewhere before.
This is your home, Tsubasa!
We have not only members of the press,
See? Takeshi's on TV, too!
but local residents gathered
here in the hopes of
What?!
getting a glimpse of the UFO!
This is the local home thought
to be concealing the alien.
Hello? I'm with The Millione Show!
I heard there was an alien here!
Oh! Paiman-san!
Wait. Does this mean there is an alien here?
We have, indeed, placed an extraterrestrial
life form under our protective custody.
Really?!
Calm down!
She is not dangerous.
Emergency
Live Broadcast!
An Alien Invasion in Nagaoka City, Niigata Prefecture?!
She could even be a savior
who's come to help this planet!
A savior?!
Will world peace finally be achieved, OD?
Oh, how fun!
This planet's been way too dangerous lately!
Oh, Utsutsu!
We'll release an official statement
on Gatchannel in the near future.
Do leave the citizens alone until then.
Oh, it's Tsubasa-chan!
Do you have a comment?
You're Tsubasa-chan?
The camera, quick!
Hey!
You idiot!
What are you thinking?!
Who are you, Mister?
JJ!
This means...
I'm gloomy.
Hey, are you recording this?
Yes...
Tsubasa.
Everyone has power that
is concealed deep within.
Only those who realize that
they possess this power
will awaken to their greater purpose.
Awaken!
Spread your as-of-yet
invisible wings...
Thy name is...
Gatchaman!
G-Gatchaman?!
Me?!
Ow...
Whoa!
What's this?!
Hmm, those wings are still blue, all right.
This is a huge scoop!
What's your name?
How do you feel about being
chosen to be a Gatchaman?!
Huh? Well...
Try to transform for us!
Huh? Transform?
Camera?!
Ready!
Go, Bird!
Huh?
Go, Bird?
Why?!
Do you have a boyfriend?
Who do you look up to?
Who's your favorite Gatchaman?
How old are you?
Hey, don't—
Do you have a boyfriend?
Are you a high school student?
Don't talk all at once!
Cut it...
out!
It's a new Gatchaman...
How do you feel?
Get out, now!
I'll deck you!
Deck?
She's saying she'll beat you all up.
What?!
Huh?!
I transformed?
How?
Oh, yeah!
The air here is great!
Exhale properly.
Huh? A new Gatchaman!
Another girl...
This is a tremendous scoop!
A New Gatchaman Is Born!
OD, do give us the lowdown later!
Who cares about those barbaric VAPE people!
This planet is still
the planet of the apes...
The First Smart Phone Elections in History!
Tachikawa City Mayoral Elections
Vote with Your Thumb
Huh?
Voting in the elections
using your smartphone?
Yeah.
You can vote once you're sixteen.
Then we can, too?
Yeah, I hear the next Prime Minister will
be chosen through smart phone votes, too.
Isn't that amazing?
Seriously?
Kae-chan, isn't that too "easy"?
Well, that's the world we live in.
Who are you trying to be?
Those are the times we live in.